[{"answer": "Crabtree!", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Who was talking about you?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, actually we hear things like that all of the time so I was a bit surprised at the reaction that mushroomed out from what Richard Sherman said.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Rachel, before we get to your interview, which is a great coo for you and for CNN and what was your reaction when you are watching it live to what he did?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Well, there isn't much about that I regret.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "What do you not regret about all of that?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "That's the short version of it.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "is that the background of all this?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "That's the -- and we're going to keep it clean.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Is that the clean version?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, I'm going to keep it clean.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Did it get nastier than that?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "You have to have that switch.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "How do you do it?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Crabtree.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Who was talking about you?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Not often really.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Do you have a problem with depression?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Not everybody in Compton is a gang member.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Did you fight a lot as a kid?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Richard, have you gone downhill since college?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I'm not afraid of anything.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "Do you feel you're untouchable?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "ICHOLS: Well, it's interesting you showed that advertisement.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "And that's what it's about, isn't it?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's really interesting because people are quick to judge and they don't know the back story.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Did you understand what he was doing?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely he said that on the telephone call.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Just to clarify, Carl, you know, Chris Christie personally said to you if you run, we're going to come after you?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, that isn't really surprising.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "What is your reaction to that denial?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I actually I want to kind of get to what their comment was because the reality is that I was approved by judges and also the law judge, the Guadagno is the one who actually pulled me off the ballot twice.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Just as an overview, Carl, before I move to the others, do you think Chris Christie therefore is a bully as many are trying to portray him?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Wait a minute.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "You were as an athlete so I don't know why you didn't expect in the political route?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Well, look.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "How do you see this playing out in the bigger picture for Chris Christie because a lot of concerns at the moment are refusing to put their heads over the parapet for him?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "I have not.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Ever met one of your victims?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "No one just sought me out.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "You know, I don't want to intrude anybody's life and, you know ...", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Why haven't you sought them out?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I thought the interview was fascinating.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "And not just to that but to the interview as a whole?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I think you're mad.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Am I madly?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Ben Ferguson, did you like the Wolf of Wall Street?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well I think that the difference in a lot of ways is the way you affect other people's lives.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Why should it be different rules for a trader given that it seems to me like he was certainly pretty sincere with the remorse he showed?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "No one is saying this about Bernie Madoff.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Leigh, (inaudible) to get in there?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Because I have no idea.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "He was?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "... I mean it's been so much terror activity ...", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "No, she's shaving it.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Is it beards staying in the Sochi games?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I think he's very ...", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "IEIRA: Why do you even encourage?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "I'm not convinced by the beard.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Don't you think he looks good in that?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Pretty extraordinary in the modern age, isn't it?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "We have a lot of crazy laws in our country, yeah.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Is that accurate?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "We already have.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "I watch CNN.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "How do you know that?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "More than you know.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "Richard, are you aware of your wife's key knowledge of the night life in Sochi?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Does that hurt (ph)?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "It was bloody painful if I'm honest with you, Richard, is it as painful as it looks?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "Well, I think you just accept it, you know, what is, what it is and I've never stopped fighting it and this stem cell trial is really a break with traditional therapies.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "How do you deal with that on an emotional level?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Well, that's part of the frustration that it is ongoing and tedious and you don't know from one day to the next what you're going to get and there are exacerbations.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "What frustrations are there for both of you about this ongoing relentlessly tedious process which is what it must be?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I'll say they're wrong.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "So those who have opposed stem cell research, what do you say to them?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "You don't want to create other Richards?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "I -- the pain in what I believe was heaven, got to the point that I was willing to down (ph) myself to hell to escape it.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "How did you eventually make that break?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "My dad was sexually abusing me starting at about eight years old continuing on up into my teenage years -- begged for help.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "ORGAN: In terms of the detail of your suffering, how bad was it?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "The stigma of having a last name Jeffs -- it's kind of a double edged sword.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "How does that stigma make you feel?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "It was completely horrible.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "To actually have lived through it, how bad was it for you?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "That's exactly the way you put it.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "When you talked together -- obviously, you worked together on this show \"Escaping the Prophet,\" do you feel a bond with other people that have been through this that nobody else can really understand?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "Flora, you both believed that the power of Warren Jeffs continues even from inside prison, is that right?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Warren is still doing church services from his prison cell.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "In what way does it manifest itself?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 683, "question": "... inside prison?", "qSentId": 682}, {"answer": "It was the scare tactic.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "And was that part of the technique, Brandon, to keep everybody under control?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "ESSOP: We are to become God's army.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "And the parallel is that you were just saying in the break there quite chillingly that part of being part of Jeffs' sect is that you're encouraged to believe that one day you will go and kill to achieve the second coming, right?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "Disciples of Warren Jeffs, I'd say there still about 10,000 plus.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Brandon, how many people are out there who are still disciples of Warren Jeffs, what he say?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "They would obey him blindly.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "And how many of those from your knowledge, from your instinct, would if it they came to it be capable of killing?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "I definitely still feel he wheels the exact same power because his word is god.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "You think he still wheels the same power even though he's imprisoned?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "You know, I want them to realize that their brain was not given to Warren Jeffs.", "docId": "140121pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "Flora, you got out, Brandon you got out, and to anyone who may be watching this who is part of this sect and completely brain washed even to the point of being murderous potentially, what do you say to them to trigger a different thought process that may make the break and escape?", "qSentId": 713}]